{"data":[{"question":"Not smoking and drinking alcohol are the most important things you can do talking care of your health.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Not smoking and drinking","b":"important things","c":"talking care","d":"your health","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Talking care-> to take care","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Gunpowder, in some ways the most effective of all the explosive materials, were a mixture of potassium nitrate, charcoal, and sulfur.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"all the","c":"were","d":"of","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Were-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"What should you do if you've finish to use your calculator?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"should","b":"if","c":"to use","d":"your calculator","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- To use-> using","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Travelling to a foreign country is always interesting, especially if it is a country that is completely different to your own.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Travelling to","b":"always interesting","c":"is completely","d":"different to","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Different to-> different from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"It is generally a best idea to place the thesis statement at or near the end of the introductory paragraph.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"best idea","b":"place","c":"at or near","d":"introductory paragraph","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Best idea-> better idea","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"There are many similarities and differences among life in the country and life in the city.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"There are","b":"similarities and differences","c":"among","d":"life","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Among-> between","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"My friends are still talking about the day while I fell in the river.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"talking about","c":"while","d":"fell in","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- While-> that","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"John found himself in a room where was very large and dark.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"himself","b":"where","c":"large","d":"dark","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Where-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Stuart stopped to write his letter because he had to leave for school.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to write","b":"because","c":"leave","d":"for school","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n-To write-> writting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"},{"question":"Janet is finally used to cook on electric stove.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"finally","c":"to cook","d":"on","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- To cook-> cooking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"32","type":"1"}]}